



- humphreys.geoff@gmail.com
- **(**352) 665 1142
- https://paradegoat.github.io /portfolio/

ABOUT

I am a community-minded innovator and thought explorer. More than a decade of starting and managing businesses has taught me that working with a team of smart, kind people to create an awesome experience for others is my idea of a good life.

SKILLS

- Ruby on Rails
 MongoDB
- Javascript
- HTML/CSS3
- Node.is
- Git
- RESTful APIs

- MySql
- PostgreSql
- Responsive
- - Web Design

EXPERIENCE

OWNER/OPERATOR

Taradiddle Design Inc | 2015 - Present

- Collaborate with clients on design and construction, and provide guidance on aesthetic and structural factors such as space planning, layout, and budget based on their needs and requests
- Maintain a design library with new products and vendors to meet the needs of varying homes and clientele
- Coordinate directly with industry leaders to deliver superior products to the client

STORE OPERATOR

Pop-A-Top | 2013 - 2015

- Designed and opened a corner store in a high traffic downtown which generated \$250,00 in the first year, with continued growth month over month
- Supervised a team of 6 employees by creating weekly schedules and task lists and developing a framework to maintain regular and honest communication

OWNER/OPERATOR

Boca Fiesta | 2009 - 2013

- Designed, built and managed a restaurant, bar and outdoor event hall with annual revenues of over \$1,000,000 and more than 50 employees
- Developed and operated the online marketing strategy, including all social media accounts and maintenance of the organization website
- Organized and coordinated daily events at the 500 person outdoor concert hall, including live music, art and film exhibits, and events with community leaders and political committees

EDUCATION

BACKEND ENGINEERING CERTIFICATE

The Iron Yard 2017

ASSOCIATE OF ARTS - AMERICAN HISTORY

Santa Fe College 2015